<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>

  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>Vasilkoff PAD Make 1.0</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>https://vasilkoff.com/pad-make</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products.</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
    <CERTIFIED>N</CERTIFIED>
    <CERTIFICATE_ID></CERTIFICATE_ID>
    <CERTIFICATE_LICENSE></CERTIFICATE_LICENSE>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>

  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>Stellare Software</Company_Name>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>https://stellare-software.lemonsqueezy.com/</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Author_First_Name>Stellare</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Software</Author_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>ecoserv301@gmail.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
  </Company_Info>

  <Program_Info>
    <Program_Name>Stellare Document Encryption</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>v6</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>04</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>02</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2026</Program_Release_Year>
    <!-- Tiered pricing: Standard £9 / Advanced £29 / Professional £59. PAD uses entry price. -->
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>9.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code>GBP</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other>9.00</Program_Cost_Other>
    <Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>Windows 10, Windows 11</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
    <Program_Installer_Type>EXE</Program_Installer_Type>
    <Program_Category_Class>Security &amp; Privacy::Encryption Tools</Program_Category_Class>
    <Program_Category_Class2>Security &amp; Privacy::Other</Program_Category_Class2>
    <Program_Specific_Category>File Encryption</Program_Specific_Category>
    <Program_Keywords>file encryption, AES-256, ChaCha20, Argon2id, document encryption, military-grade encryption, triple-pass encryption, machine-bound license, right-click encryption, brute force protection, Windows encryption tool, secure files, PDF encryption, secure documents, file security</Program_Keywords>
    <Expire_Count>0</Expire_Count>
    <Expire_Based_On>Launches</Expire_Based_On>
    <Expire_Other_Time></Expire_Other_Time>
    <Expire_Warn_Days>0</Expire_Warn_Days>
    <Expire_Warn_Times>0</Expire_Warn_Times>
  </Program_Info>

  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://stellare-software.lemonsqueezy.com/</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://stellare-software.lemonsqueezy.com/checkout/buy/e7f6be3b-b91d-4ed2-92d2-ef11c4b0e257</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://github.com/ecoserv301-dotcom/Stellare-Document-Encryption/raw/refs/heads/main/SDE%20PRO%20v124.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>https://github.com/ecoserv301-dotcom/Stellare-Document-Encryption/raw/refs/heads/main/stellare_preview-2.ico</Application_Icon_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>https://github.com/ecoserv301-dotcom/Stellare-Document-Encryption/raw/refs/heads/main/StellareDocumentEncryptionSetup_v6.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>

  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>

      <!-- 45 characters max — 45 chars exactly -->
      <Char_Desc_45>Military-grade triple-pass AES-256 encryption</Char_Desc_45>

      <!-- 80 characters max — 77 chars -->
      <Char_Desc_80>Triple-pass AES-256 file encryption with Argon2id key derivation for Windows.</Char_Desc_80>

      <!-- 150 characters max — 141 chars -->
      <Char_Desc_150>Stellare Document Encryption protects any file with triple-pass AES-256, ChaCha20 and Argon2id. Machine-bound licensing. 3 tiers from £9.</Char_Desc_150>

      <!-- 250 characters max — 247 chars -->
      <Char_Desc_250>Stellare Document Encryption uses a triple-pass cipher stack (AES-256 + ChaCha20 + AES-256) with Argon2id key derivation to protect any file type. Right-click shell integration, brute-force resistance, and machine-bound licensing in 3 tiers from £9.</Char_Desc_250>

      <!-- 450 characters max — 444 chars -->
      <Char_Desc_450>Stellare Document Encryption is a military-grade file encryption tool for Windows. It uses triple-pass AES-256, ChaCha20 and Argon2id key derivation to protect any file type. Features include right-click shell integration, machine-bound hardware licensing, brute-force resistance and a built-in PDF user manual. Available in Standard (£9), Advanced (£29) and Professional (£59) tiers. Installs and uninstalls cleanly with no residual data.</Char_Desc_450>

      <!-- Full description — used by sites that accept longer text -->
      <Char_Desc_2000>Stellare Document Encryption (SDE) v6 is a professional-grade file encryption application for Windows 10 and Windows 11. Built for individuals and businesses who need reliable, hardware-bound protection for sensitive documents, SDE applies a triple-pass cipher stack that is resistant to brute-force attack and keyed to your machine.

HOW IT WORKS:
SDE encrypts any file — PDF, DOCX, images, archives, executables — using a three-layer cipher stack: AES-256 first pass, ChaCha20 mid-pass, and AES-256 final pass. Keys are derived using Argon2id with a configurable work factor, meaning brute-force attacks are computationally expensive by design. The encrypted output is machine-bound — it can only be decrypted on the hardware it was locked to, preventing unauthorised redistribution.

KEY FEATURES:
- Triple-pass cipher stack: AES-256 + ChaCha20 + AES-256
- Argon2id key derivation — hardened against GPU and dictionary attacks
- KFM-Controlled Encryption Depth — key file mechanism for additional key material
- Machine-bound licensing — hardware-locked, cannot be transferred without re-activation
- Right-click Windows shell integration — encrypt or decrypt any file from Explorer
- Built-in PDF user manual — full documentation included in the installer
- Brute-force secure mode (Professional tier) — maximum resistance configuration
- Clean install and uninstall — no residual encrypted data or registry junk
- Compatible with Windows 10 and Windows 11

THREE TIERS:
Standard (£9) — Core triple-pass encryption, right-click shell integration, machine-bound licensing, 7 core features.
Advanced (£29) — All Standard features plus Advanced Key File mode, expanded cipher options, 8 features.
Professional (£59) — All Advanced features plus Brute Force Secure mode, maximum Argon2id hardening, priority activation, 8 features.

WHO IT IS FOR:
Individuals protecting sensitive personal documents on shared or portable machines. Small businesses encrypting client files before cloud storage or email. Developers and IT professionals who need a scriptable, hardware-bound encryption layer without relying on cloud key management. Anyone who needs file-level encryption that works without an internet connection.

SDE v6 is compiled natively with Nuitka and packaged with Inno Setup — no Python runtime is distributed, and the binary is not a wrapper. What you install is a standalone Windows application.</Char_Desc_2000>

    </English>
  </Program_Descriptions>

</XML_DIZ_INFO>
